{
    "subject": "resource/Renegades_of_Funk",
    "predicate": "property/label",
    "object": "resource/Tommy_Boy_Records",
    "human_readable": "The label of Renegades of Funk is Tommy Boy Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8589343428611755,
            "question": "What record label is associated with Renegades of Funk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8469898104667664,
            "question": "Is Renegades of Funk signed to a record label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6555975675582886,
            "question": "Are there any famous albums released by Renegades of Funk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6494845151901245,
            "question": "Who or what is Tommy Boy Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5255711078643799,
            "question": "What genre of music might Renegades of Funk produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5130348801612854,
            "question": "What is the history of Tommy Boy Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4814971685409546,
            "question": "What is the impact of Tommy Boy Records on music history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4373011887073517,
            "question": "How has Renegades of Funk influenced the music industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4353652596473694,
            "question": "Has Tommy Boy Records won any awards for its music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40502503514289856,
            "question": "Can you name any other artists signed to Tommy Boy Records?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Renegades of Funk is Tommy Boy Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3796_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Tommy Boy Records won any awards for its music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3796_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Renegades of Funk influenced the music industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3796_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the impact of Tommy Boy Records on music history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3796_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3796_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents all mention that the track \"Renegades Of Funk\" has a label of \"Tommy Boy\", which supports the triple statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information confirms that the record \"Renegades Of Funk\" by Afrika Bambaataa and Soulsonic Force was released on the Tommy Boy Records label."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}